TAI PHAM

Full Stack Developer specializing in Javascript with **3.5 years experience**. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for **Front end** and **Back end** projects. Operated in numerous **Javascript** frameworks, libraries and databases. Deployed projects on **AWS**. Coordinated a team of fresher and junior developers. Always ready for a new challenge.

Technical Skills

- Frontend: HTML, CSS, React, React Native, Redux, Jquery, Websocket, Socketio, Emotion, Styled-component, Material-UI, Ant design, Openlayers.
- Backend: Express, Fastify, Sail, Serverless framework.
- Database: Postgres, MySQL, MariaDB, Mongodb, Redis.
- Search engine: Elasticsearch.
- Cloud service: Cloudfront, S3, EC2, RDS, Lambda, API gateway, Elasticsearch service.

Container: Docker.Web Server: Nginx.

Work Experience

Position	Company	Duration
Full Stack Developer	Spiritlabs	10/2018 to present
Front End Developer	Saigon Technology Solutions	9/2017 to 10/2018
Front End Developer	Robert Bosch Engineering and Business Solutions	08/2016 to 09/2017

Projects

SFF x Switch Go

- **Description**: Youtube-like video platform focusing in Fintech.
- Role: Team lead, working directly with BA and PM to plan tasks and features. Coordinated teamwork
 using agile approach. Initialized and contributed for both FE and BE. Supporting team member to
 overcome issues.
- Tech: React, Redux, SocketIO, Fastify, MongoDB, Elasticsearch.
- Service: AWS EC2, AWS S3, Videospace, Gevme
- Page: https://go.sffxswitch.com

Hex Safe

• Description: Institutional custody for cryptocurrencies.

- Role: Full stack developer, working with designer and Back end team for smooth FE integration.

 Helped defining API. Prepare API for upcoming features. Contributed to In-house Node framework.
- Tech: React, Redux, JQuery, Express, MariaDB.
- Page: https://hextrust.com

Teemie

- **Description**: Management tool built specifically for industries where managers and staff are on the go!.
- Role: Front end developer, contributed to both web (manager) and mobile (staff) version.
- Tech: React, Redux, React native, Sail, MongoDB.
- Service: AWS EC2, AWS S3, Visual Studio App Center
- Page: https://teemieapp.com

Fluentup

- Description: Online language learning platform.
- Role: Back end developer, part-time front end to keep project release in time.
- Tech: Sail, MongoDB.
- Service: AWS EC2, AWS S3.Page: https://fluentup.com/

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science - Sep 2016

Ton Duc Thang University, Ho Chi Minh

Contact

- +84 909 840 720
- District 7, Ho Chi Minh
- Github
- Linkedin
- phamtai2119@gmail.com